Eren Süleymanoğlu

Full Stack Developer

0539-504-0870 • erensuleymanoglu@gmail.com • eren.codes



Summary

Hi, I'm Eren. Fullstack Developer who loves to code and design experiences on the web. With a passion for coding and an eye for design, I craft seamless online journeys using CSS, JavaScript, Python, React, TypeScript and Solidity.

Experience

Full Stack Developer

Freelance Web Developer 2018 - Present

I'm now a full stack developer working as a freelancer. My stack includes Solidity, CSS, React, Next.js, TypeScript, Tailwind, SQL and WordPress. I'm open to full-time remote opportunities.

Wordpress Developer

VigitalArt

2016 - 2018

We were building premium themes for Envato Market using CSS3, Javascript (jQuery) and Visual Composer integrated with WordPress CMS.

Full Stack Developer

BTdays Technology 2014 - 2016

I helped build a customer loyalty platform which is written in Python using Django Framework called JokerKart. I worked as both backend and frontend developer. Also, my other responsibility was managing Git repos.

Frontend Developer

Novospire

2013 - 2014

I worked as a frontend developer. I've built websites using CSS3 and Javascript (jQuery) integrated with WordPress CMS.

Full Stack Developer

Restoranya Inc.

2009 - 2013 (4 years)

Restoranya was an online food delivery platform that was written in Python using Django Framework. I worked as both a backend and frontend developer. Also, my other responsibilities were managing Git repos, databases and servers.

Intern

Pastelboya Interactive 2008 - 2009

I've learned how to design websites and web applications. I've built my frontend and backend skills.

Language

English - Full Proficiency

Education

Beykent University

Bachelor, Computer Software Engineering 2012 - 2017

Sakıp Sabancı Anadolu Lisesi

Mathematics 2003 - 2007

Skills

```
Python • JavaScript • NextJS • React • TypeScript • CSS 3 • HTML 5 • NoSQL • SQL • Solidity • NodeJS • jQuery • Git
```